Finding Aid for the Benjamin Aaron Papers LSC.0413
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Latchford Glass Co. and GPPAW: No. 85-19-82 (D. McCullough), 1983 Feb 10 (Box 50, Folder 4)
- Long Beach Press-Telegram and Los Angeles Newspaper Guild, Local 69, 1997 Dec 9 (Box 50, Folder 5)
- LA County Employee Relations Commission Mediate of Dispute Between AFSCME, Local 685 and LA County (Probation Dept.), 1970 (Box 50, Folder 6)
- Lucent Technologies and CWA Grievance No. 94-48, 1997 July 17 (Box 50, Folder 7)
- McClatchy Newspapers Decisions, 1976 (Box 50, Folder 8)
- Arb. Southern California Edison and Local 246, UWUA, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 9)
- Arb. Major Safe Co. and United Steel Workers (Guzman, Valentine, Ruiz), 1975 (Box 50, Folder 10)
- Manville Products Corp. and International Chemical Workers Union Local No. 146 72 300 0315 89, 1990 Apr 26 (Box 50, Folder 11)
- McDonald Douglas Helicopter Co. and Electric & Technicians, Local 1553 72 300 0111 88, 1988 Nov 22 (Box 50, Folder 12)
- MGM-Desert Inn Hotel & Casino Culinary Workers Union, Local 226, 1988 Oct 14 (Box 50, Folder 13)
- Miramar Sheraton Hotel and HERE, Local 814 (Delmy Falla), 1999 Dec 14 (Box 50, Folder 14)
- Mt. States T & T Co. and CWA Grievance No. 80CN148 (Sponberg), 1982 (Box 50, Folder 15)
- Nabisco Foods and Teamsters Union Local 186 Case # 72 300 00238 93, 1994 Aug 29 (Box 50, Folder 16)
- Arb. NBC and NABET Case 74-30-0115-78; Grievance NS 78-205, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 17)
- National Airlines and ALPA MIA # 49-79 (R.W. Pech, et al.), 1979 (Box 50, Folder 18)
- Northwest-Republic Pilots, 1991 Jan 8 (Box 50, Folder 19)
- Arbitration Northwest Airlines and Arline Pilots Association (Grievance No. 75-29 (M. Ginzl)), 1975-1976 (Box 50, Folder 20)
- Owens-Brockway Glass Containers and Class, Molders & Allied Workers No. 28-34-90-14 (J. Abelar), 1990 Nov 13 (Box 50, Folder 21)
- Owens Brockway and GMPPAW Case No. 137-88-31 (M. Navarrete), 1989 Jul 13 (Box 50, Folder 22)
- Owens-Illinois, Inc. GPPAW Grievance No. 137M-86-01 (R. Taylor), 1986 Nov 25 (Box 50, Folder 23)
- Arb. Owens-Illinois, Inc. and GBBA: Grievance No. 137-119-P-77 et al., 1978 (Box 50, Folder 24)
- Arb. Owens-Illinois, Inc. and GBBA: No. 177-77-64 and 177-77-66, 1977 (Box 50, Folder 25)
- Arb. PG & E and IBEW, Local 1245 Case No. 72 (E. Butler), 1978 (Box 50, Folder 26)
- Pan American World Airways - Union of Flight Attendants, 1984-1986 (Box 50, Folder 27)
- Pasadena Unified School District - United Teachers of Pasadena Case No. 72 390 0243 89, 1990 (Box 50, Folder 28)
- Plaza B.G. and Culinary Workers Union Local 226 (Jo Ann Kim), 2006 July 11 (Box 50, Folder 29)
- Plaza Hotel and Culinary Workers Local 226 (Evelyn Allen), 1996 Nov 18 (Box 50, Folder 30)
- Press Democrat and Northern California Newspaper Guild Local 52 (Jeff Moriarity), 1997 July 9 (Box 50, Folder 31)
- Press Democrat and Northern California Newspaper Guild, Local 52 (Richard Mellott), 1996 Aug 27 (Box 50, Folder 32)
- Press-Telegram and Los Angeles Newspaper Guild Case No. 72 300 00140 94, 1994 Oct 18 (Box 50, Folder 33)
- Arb. Sacramento Newspaper Publishers Association and Sacramento Printing Pressmen Union No. 60, 1974 (Box 50, Folder 34)
- Safeway Store No. 1733 and United Food & Commercial Workers Local 99 (Susie McCauley), 2004 Apr 29 (Box 50, Folder 35)
- Safeway Inc. and United Food & Commercial Workers Local 99 (Store No. 1706 Recognition), 2001 Jun 19 (Box 50, Folder 36)
- Safeway Stores, Inc. and Teamsters Local No. 856, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 37)
- San Antonio Light and San Antonio Guild Local 25 (Steve Wilson Layoff), 1992 Feb 6 (Box 50, Folder 38)
- Arb. San Francisco Progress and Office and Professional Employees Local 3, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 39)
- Jos. Schlitz Bewing Co., Container Div. and Steel Workers, 1984 Apr 19 (Box 50, Folder 40)
- Ameritech and IBEW Local 21 (Rory Seleman) Downers Grove, IL, 2005 Apr 19 (Box 50, Folder 41)
- Arb. Joseph Schlitz Brewing Co. and Steel Workers Local 8433: Grievance LA-USW-44-78, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 42)
- SEIU Local No. 99 Case No. 72 673 0001 91, 1991 Nov 13 (Box 50, Folder 43)
- Sequoia Pacific and United Paperworkers International Union Case No. 72 300 0403 89, 1991 Oct 24 (Box 50, Folder 44)
- Showboat Hotel & Casino and Culinary Workers Union, Local 226, 1999 Dec 7 (Box 50, Folder 45)
- Showboat Hotel & Casino and Culinary Workers Union Local 226 Decisions, 1994 (Box 50, Folder 46)
- Sonoma State University, CSUC and Sandra L. Davis, 1984 (Box 50, Folder 47)
- Southern California Edison Co. and Local 246, IBEW, 1977 (Box 50, Folder 48)
- Southern California Rapid Transit District Decisions, 1974-1989 (Box 50, Folder 49)
- Arb. Standard Oil Co. of California and Petroleum Workers Union, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 50)
- Stanford University Faculty Discipline Mark G. Perlroth, MD (Box 50, Folder 51)
- Stardust Hotel/Casino and Culinary Workers Union Local 226 (Helps, Hall Cooks & Uniform Room Attendants), 2002 Feb 11 (Box 50, Folder 52)
- Stardust Hotel/Casino and Culinary Workers Union Local 226 (Leo and Cox), 1998 June 17 (Box 50, Folder 53)
- Stardust Hotel and Casino Decisions, 1994 (Box 50, Folder 54)
- Stratosphere Tower & Casino and Culinary Workers Union Local 226 (Vicki Lynch), 2004 Mar 11 (Box 50, Folder 55)
- Technicolor and IATSE, Local 165, 1983 Dec 19 (Box 50, Folder 56)
- Arb. Television Station KOVR and AFTRA (Stockton Studio Operation), 1978 (Box 50, Folder 57)
- Arb. Television Station KOVR and AFTRA, 1976 (Box 50, Folder 58)
- Texaco Refining & Marketing and Oil, Chemical & Atomic Workers, Local No. 1-219 Grievance TRMI-4-1988, 1989 Apr 20 (Box 50, Folder 59)
- Timet and USA 81-146, 82-2, (81-90-82-3), 1983 Feb 3 (Box 50, Folder 60)
- Transamerica Airlines and ALPA, 1980 (Box 50, Folder 61)
- Transportation Leasing Co. and Amal. Council of Greyhound Local Unions (Allentown), 1987 July 27-28 (Box 50, Folder 62)
- Trans-World Airlines (Box 50, Folder 63)
- Tropicana Resort and Casino and Culinary Workers Union, Local 226 (Box 50, Folder 64)
- Unisource Georgia-Pacific and ILWU, Local 6 (Dennis Desmond) Oakland, CA, 2002 Feb 18 (Box 50, Folder 65)
- Union Oil Co. and OCAW, Local 1-675 Case No. 300 00101 95, 1995 Aug 16 (Box 50, Folder 66)
- Union Plaza Hotel and Culinary Workers, Local 226 (Annette Robertson), 1995 June 20 (Box 50, Folder 67)
- United Air Lines and ALPA System Board of Adjustment General File (Box 50, Folder 68)
- United Airline and ALPA Decisions, 1987-1990 (Box 50, Folder 69)
- UAW Public Review Board, 2006 (Box 51, Folder 1)
- UAW Public Review Board, 2005 (Box 51, Folder 2)
- UAW Public Review Board, 2004 (Box 51, Folder 3)
- UAW Public Review Board, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 4)
- UAW Public Review Board, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 5)
- UAW Public Review Board, 2001 (Box 51, Folder 6)
- UAW Public Review Board, 2000 (Box 51, Folder 7)
- UAW Public Review Board, 1999 (Box 51, Folder 8)
- UAW Public Review Board, 1998 (Box 51, Folder 9)
- UAW Public Review Board, 1997 (Box 51, Folder 10)
- UAW Public Review Board, 1996 (Box 51, Folder 11)
- UAW Public Review Board, 1995 (Box 51, Folder 12)
- UAW Public Review Board, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 13)
- UAW Public Review Board, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 14)
- UAW Public Review Board, 1992 (Box 51, Folder 15)
- UAW Public Review Board, 1991 (Box 51, Folder 16)
- UAW Public Review Board Reports (Box 51, Folder 17)
- International Labor Law Reports, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 1)
- International Labor Law Reports, 1981-1984 (Box 52, Folder 2)
- International Labor Law Reports, 1974-1980 (Box 52, Folder 3)
- Arbitration Due Process Protocol (Box 52, Folder 4)
- IRRA Spring Meeting, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 5)
- Labor Management Committee for Review of EERA, SEERA, and HEERA (Box 52, Folder 6)
- Public Sector Bargaining (2nd ed), 1997 (Box 52, Folder 7)
- AAA 10th Annual Arbitration Day, 1997 Nov 10 (Box 52, Folder 8)
- Labor Law Group Casebook on Comparative Labor Law, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 9)
- ALI-ABA Advanced Seminar on Labor and Employment Law Pepperdine, 1987 Jul 14 (Box 52, Folder 10)
- New Trends in Labor Law in the US, 1987 Mar 24 (Box 52, Folder 11)
- Australian Industrial Relations Materials (Box 52, Folder 12)
- Federation of Netherlands Industry, 1986 Sep 12 (Box 52, Folder 13)
- 50th Anniversary Symposium on the NLRB-Stanford Law School, 1985 Oct 4-5 (Box 52, Folder 14)
- Institute of Industrial Relations Conference on Worker's Rights, 1985 Dec 4 (Box 52, Folder 15)
- IBM Employee Relations Conference, 1984 Jun 12 (Box 52, Folder 16)
- AAA Second Annual Employment Law and Practice Conference San Diego, 1984 Jun 7 (Box 52, Folder 17)
- Board of Inquiry: Los Angeles County Metropolitan Transportation Authority and United Transportation Union, Amalgamated Transit Union, and Transportation Communications Unions, 3 Jul 2000 (Box 53, Folder 1)
- Board of Inquiry: Los Angeles County Metropolitan Transportation Authority and United Transportation Union, 2003 Jul 15 (Box 53, Folder 2)
- MTA Comprehensive Proposal to UTU, 2003 Jun 24 (Box 53, Folder 3)
- IRRA Symposium on a Half Century of Collective Bargaining - US Style, 1997 Jan 3 (Box 53, Folder 4)
- IRRA Panel on Wage Controls, Chicago, 1998 Jan 4 (Box 53, Folder 5)
- Arlington Crane, Butters & Oberlein, 1986 (Box 53, Folder 6)
- League of California Cities, 1970 Mar 6 (Box 53, Folder 7)
- M-M-B Conference, 1990 Aug (Box 53, Folder 8)
- American Gas Association Section Conference - Salt Lake City, 1968 May 14 (Box 53, Folder 9)
- Conference on Collective Bargaining in the Postal Service, 1970 Oct 9 (Box 53, Folder 10)
- Townhall Speech on Employee Relations Ordinance, 1968 Aug 9 (Box 53, Folder 11)
- Governor's Conference on Public Employment Relations (New York), 1968 Oct 14 (Box 53, Folder 12)
- Beverly Hills BAR Association - Labor Law Program, 1968 Dec 5 (Box 53, Folder 13)
- Journal of Air Law and Commerce Symposium on the Railway Labor Act and the Airlines, 1969 Mar 26-28 (Box 53, Folder 14)
- United States Postal Service regional Arbitration Decisions, 1972-1975 (Box 53, Folder 15)
- United States Postal Service regional Arbitration Decisions, 1976-1978 (Box 53, Folder 16)
- IIR 25th Anniversary Conference, 1970 Oct 17 (Box 53, Folder 17)
- Arb. US Steel Corp. and Industrial Police Association Local Unions, 1975 (Box 53, Folder 18)
- ILLR (Box 53, Folder 19)
- Sabbatical Leave Correspondence (Box 53, Folder 20)
- UCLA Institute of Industrial Relations Advisory Committee, 2000-2001 (Box 53, Folder 21)
- IIR (Box 53, Folder 22)
- John Shepard Wiley Jr. (Box 53, Folder 23)
- Mark Freedland (Box 53, Folder 24)
- Panel on Public Employee Representation, 1969 Apr 14 (Box 53, Folder 25)
- "Impasse Procedures - How to Use Them and Will They Stop Strikes?" League of California Cities, Labor Relations Institute San Francisco, 1971 Mar 18 (Box 53, Folder 26)
- Technological Change and Labor Management Relations, 1967 May (Box 53, Folder 27)
- Lecture on Emergency Disputes University of Wisconsin, 1969 Apr 24 (Box 53, Folder 28)
- KMPC Inquiry Interview, 1971 Jun 20 (Box 53, Folder 29)
- Beverly Hills BAR Association, Labor Law Committee, Panel Discussion on Boys Market Case, 1970 Oct 29 (Box 53, Folder 30)
- American Assembly: Arden House Conference on Public Employment, 1971 Jan 22 (Box 53, Folder 31)
- IIR (Berkeley) Conference on "Phase 1 to Phase 2: The New Economic Policy in Transition", 1971 Nov 23 (Box 53, Folder 32)
- IRRA, Southern California Chapter Panel on Incomes Policies, 1972 Apr 19 (Box 53, Folder 33)
- West Coast Assembly on Collective Bargaining in the Public Service, 1972 May (Box 53, Folder 34)
- United Airlines and Association of Flight Attendants, 1974-1978 (Box 54, Folder 1)
- United Expositions Service and Sign, Scene, Pictorial Painters, Local No. 831 Case # 72 300 035389, 1990 Feb 17 (Box 54, Folder 2)
- United Parcel Service and Independent Pilots Ass'n, 1997 Jun 5 (Box 54, Folder 3)
- United Parcel Service Co. and Independent Pilots Ass'n Case No. 92-258, 92-222, 1993 Feb 25 (Box 54, Folder 4)
- United States Postal Service Arbitration Decisions, 1982-1983 (Box 54, Folder 5)
- United States Postal Service Arbitration Decision, 1984-1985 (Box 54, Folder 6)
- Unocal Corp. and International Union of Petroleum and Industrial Workers Case No. 72 300 0244 92, 1992 Nov 17 (Box 54, Folder 7)
- Arb. Varig Brazilian Airlines and District 100, IAMAWA, 1978, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 8)
- Ventura Community College Fed'n. of Teachers AFT Local 1828 (Agency Fee/ Fair Share), 1982 Feb 28 (Box 54, Folder 9)
- Vons and United Food and Commerical Workers, Local 1036 (Estrada), 2003 Mar 25 (Box 54, Folder 10)
- West Air Commuter Airlines and ALPA (Martin Springfield), 1995 Oct 19-20 (Box 54, Folder 11)
- West Air Commuter Airlines - ALPA General File (Box 54, Folder 12)
- Western Union and CWA/United Telegraph Workers (Harold Paz) case No. 72 300 0429 88, 1988 Dec 13-14 (Box 54, Folder 13)
- Witco Chemical Corp. and OCAW, Local No. 1-219. Case no. 72 300 0390 89 (J. Vasquez), 1990 May 10 (Box 54, Folder 14)
- Appeals Filed by Wilbert Sonnier on Behalf of UAW Local Union 148 (Box 54, Folder 15)
- Undocketed Appeal of Deniese Alejandro, Member UAW Local Union 2244 (Fremont, CA) vs. UAW International Ex. Board Region 5 (Box 54, Folder 16)
- Appeal of Deborah Torres vs. UAW Local Union 594 Ex. Board (Pontiac, MI) Region 1 (Box 54, Folder 17)
- Appeal of Greg Shotwell, Member, Local Union 1753, UAW (Lancing, MI) Reg. 1C vs. UAW general Motors Department (Box 54, Folder 18)
- Appeal of Tyrone Wilson vs. UAW Local Union 1976 membership (Ypsilanti, MI) Region 1A (Box 54, Folder 19)
- Appeal of Alan King, Member, Local Union 685, UAW (Kokomo, IN) Region 3 vs. UAW National Daimler Chrysler Dept. (Box 54, Folder 20)
- Appeal of James B. O'Connor, et al vs. Local Union 974, UAW (East Peoria, IL) Region 4 (Box 54, Folder 21)
- Appeal of Kelly Palmer vs. Local Union 668, UAW (Saginaw, MI) Region 1D (Box 54, Folder 22)
- Appeal of Ron Willis vs. Local Union 1999, UAW (Oklahoma City, OK) Region 5 (Box 54, Folder 23)
- Appeal of Norm McComb in the Matter of Tom Carmahan vs. UAW Local Union 659 (Flint, MI) Region 1C (Box 54, Folder 24)
- UAW Public Review Board (Box 54, Folder 25)
- National Academy of Arbitrators, 1997 (Box 55, Folder 1)
- National Academy of Arbitrators 50th Annual Meeting, 1997 May (Box 55, Folder 2)
- NAA Committee on International Studies, 2000 (Box 55, Folder 3)
- NAA Fall Education Conference, 1999, 2000 Oct 27-29 (Box 55, Folder 4)
- National Academy of Arbitrators Annual Meeting, 1996 (Box 55, Folder 5)
- National Academy of Arbitrators, 1996 (Box 55, Folder 6)
- National Academy of Arbitrators, 1994-1995 (Box 55, Folder 7)
- National Academy of Arbitrators, 1993 (Box 55, Folder 8)
- National Academy of Arbitrators, 1992 (Box 55, Folder 9)
- National Academy of Arbitrators, 1990-1991 (Box 55, Folder 10)
- National Academy of Arbitrators, 1989 (Box 55, Folder 11)
- George E. Marshall Jr. (Box 55, Folder 12)
- Committee on Professional Responsibility and Grievances, 1991 (Box 55, Folder 13)
- Committee on Professional Responsibility and Grievances, 1990 (Box 55, Folder 14)
- National Academy of Arbitrators Committee on Professional Responsibility on Grievances, 1985-1988 (Box 55, Folder 15)
- National Academy of Arbitrators Committee on Professional Responsibility and Ethics, 1979-1984 (Box 55, Folder 16)
- National Academy of Arbitrators, Ethics and Grievance Committee, 1972-1978 (Box 55, Folder 17)
- NAA International Studies Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 55, Folder 18)
- NAA Committee on International Studies: Impact of Electronic Technology on Workplace Disputes - Ron McCallum (Australia), 2001 Sep 1 (Box 55, Folder 19)
- Benjamin Aaron lecture DVD, 2006
  "New Perspectives on Workers' Rights."
- United States Postal Service National Arbitration Panel, 1979 (Box 56, Folder 1)
- United States Postal Service Arbitration Decisions, 1978-1980 (Box 56, Folder 2)
- Steel Negotiations, 1974 (Box 56, Folder 3)
- Basic Steel Negotiations, 1977 (Box 56, Folder 4)
- Coordinating Committee Steel Companies - United Steel Workers. ENA-80 (Box 56, Folder 5)
- National Labor Organization Committee of Experts, 1994 (Box 56, Folder 6)
- ILO General Survey of Convention No. 15C and Recommendation No. 165, 1993 (Box 56, Folder 7)
- COE, 1993-1994 (Box 56, Folder 8)
- International Labor Organization Committee of Experts, 1993 (Box 56, Folder 9)
- International Labor Organization Committee of Experts, 1992 (Box 56, Folder 10)
- International Labor Organization Committee of Experts, 1991 (Box 56, Folder 11)
- International Labor Organization Committee of Experts, 1990 (Box 56, Folder 12)
- International Labor Organization Committee of Experts, 1989 (Box 56, Folder 13)
- International Labor Organization Committee of Experts, 1988 (Box 56, Folder 14)
- International Labor Organization Committee of Experts, 1985-1987 (Box 56, Folder 15)
- US National Branch, ISLLSS, 2003- (Box 56, Folder 16)
- US National Branch, ISLLSS, 1985-2002 (Box 56, Folder 17)
- International Society for Labor and Social Security Law, 2004 (Box 56, Folder 18)